[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "You guys want to step in?", "question_tokens": ["You", "guys", "want", "to", "step", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Identify yourselves?", "question_tokens": ["Identify", "yourselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I'm Betty.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "Betty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "Three generations of family?", "question_tokens": ["Three", "generations", "of", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "So what was it like?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "was", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "It made you appreciate hot water, flushing toilets, electricity.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "made", "you", "appreciate", "hot", "water", ",", "flushing", "toilets", ",", "electricity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "But you came through it as a family?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "came", "through", "it", "as", "a", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: We did.", "answer_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "FEMALE", ":", "We", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Were you worried at any point it might not end this way?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "worried", "at", "any", "point", "it", "might", "not", "end", "this", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Yes, the first night was rough because we were tilting very badly.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "first", "night", "was", "rough", "because", "we", "were", "tilting", "very", "badly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "The ship was listing, right?", "question_tokens": ["The", "ship", "was", "listing", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Yes, very badly.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "very", "badly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "And what was it like for you guys?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "For me, it was really scary because it's never happened to me, and it's my first cruise.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", ",", "it", "was", "really", "scary", "because", "it", "'s", "never", "happened", "to", "me", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "my", "first", "cruise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Good to have your mom and grand mom and everybody with you, so you were safe?", "question_tokens": ["Good", "to", "have", "your", "mom", "and", "grand", "mom", "and", "everybody", "with", "you", ",", "so", "you", "were", "safe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ma'am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["June"], "LOCATION": ["Alaska"]}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "So, are you going to go on a cruise again?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "are", "you", "going", "to", "go", "on", "a", "cruise", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I actually have one booked in June for Alaska.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "have", "one", "booked", "in", "June", "for", "Alaska", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How do you past the time?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "past", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I had packed some cards.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "packed", "some", "cards", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Are you, and are you going to sue them?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", ",", "and", "are", "you", "going", "to", "sue", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I feel like they didn't start off right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "they", "did", "n't", "start", "off", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Did you think they kept you informed, and do you feel you were constantly given the right information?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "they", "kept", "you", "informed", ",", "and", "do", "you", "feel", "you", "were", "constantly", "given", "the", "right", "information", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "It was constantly changing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "constantly", "changing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Are they safe and sound if they're feeling OK or not?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "safe", "and", "sound", "if", "they", "'re", "feeling", "OK", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, I think the most important thing is definitely get to a warm shower, a nice bed, and get some rest, because honestly, time will tell what we're going to see in the next couple days from this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "is", "definitely", "get", "to", "a", "warm", "shower", ",", "a", "nice", "bed", ",", "and", "get", "some", "rest", ",", "because", "honestly", ",", "time", "will", "tell", "what", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "see", "in", "the", "next", "couple", "days", "from", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "This is Rusty, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "Rusty", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Excited to be on land.", "answer_tokens": ["Excited", "to", "be", "on", "land", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Do you think you realized because of this and because of what happened, maybe if it was a regular cruise you might not feel this way, and now you appreciate them in a way you didn't?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "realized", "because", "of", "this", "and", "because", "of", "what", "happened", ",", "maybe", "if", "it", "was", "a", "regular", "cruise", "you", "might", "not", "feel", "this", "way", ",", "and", "now", "you", "appreciate", "them", "in", "a", "way", "you", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ma'am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Your mom and dad, what was it like to see her?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "mom", "and", "dad", ",", "what", "was", "it", "like", "to", "see", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Oh, my word.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Where are you headed now?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "headed", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "To the hotel to eat, I hope.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "the", "hotel", "to", "eat", ",", "I", "hope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "This was your surprise 40th birthday party?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "your", "surprise", "40th", "birthday", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What did you have for food?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "have", "for", "food", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "They fed us lots of food.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "fed", "us", "lots", "of", "food", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Which would you prefer, a shower or a toilet?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "would", "you", "prefer", ",", "a", "shower", "or", "a", "toilet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, and they got the toilets working today, so we have been using those but probably a hot shower is probably what our pro priority is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "they", "got", "the", "toilets", "working", "today", ",", "so", "we", "have", "been", "using", "those", "but", "probably", "a", "hot", "shower", "is", "probably", "what", "our", "pro", "priority", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "So how was it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "It was kind of crazy, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "kind", "of", "crazy", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kansas City", "Topeka"]}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "AVIDGE: And where are they right now?", "question_tokens": ["AVIDGE", ":", "And", "where", "are", "they", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "They're back in Kansas City, in Topeka.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "back", "in", "Kansas", "City", ",", "in", "Topeka", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "I mean, how is it we see you and other still people waiting?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "is", "it", "we", "see", "you", "and", "other", "still", "people", "waiting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "He's a platinum member.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "platinum", "member", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "And what has it been like just in the past few hours here waiting to finally finish this ordeal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "has", "it", "been", "like", "just", "in", "the", "past", "few", "hours", "here", "waiting", "to", "finally", "finish", "this", "ordeal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "It's -- well, today, the mood kind of turned negative, as everyone started listening to what was happening onshore.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "well", ",", "today", ",", "the", "mood", "kind", "of", "turned", "negative", ",", "as", "everyone", "started", "listening", "to", "what", "was", "happening", "onshore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "You know, just tell us about -- was that a cathartic type of thing?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "just", "tell", "us", "about", "--", "was", "that", "a", "cathartic", "type", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Yes, tweets are just cathartic to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "tweets", "are", "just", "cathartic", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "You actually have a coat and are not freezing?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "have", "a", "coat", "and", "are", "not", "freezing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I have a sweater on right now, but I brought about five books and eight magazines and we have read them al cover to cover.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "sweater", "on", "right", "now", ",", "but", "I", "brought", "about", "five", "books", "and", "eight", "magazines", "and", "we", "have", "read", "them", "al", "cover", "to", "cover", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Did that happen for you also?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "happen", "for", "you", "also", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What was the -- if there's a moment, you talk about what was the worst single thing that happened and maybe the best single thing that happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "--", "if", "there", "'s", "a", "moment", ",", "you", "talk", "about", "what", "was", "the", "worst", "single", "thing", "that", "happened", "and", "maybe", "the", "best", "single", "thing", "that", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, the worst was -- I'm going to have to say the fire.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "worst", "was", "--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "have", "to", "say", "the", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Well, get on that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "get", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Glad to be on land, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Glad", "to", "be", "on", "land", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans", "South Carolina"]}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "To get on the bus to go to New Orleans?", "question_tokens": ["To", "get", "on", "the", "bus", "to", "go", "to", "New", "Orleans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "New Orleans, and then fly out tomorrow to South Carolina.", "answer_tokens": ["New", "Orleans", ",", "and", "then", "fly", "out", "tomorrow", "to", "South", "Carolina", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "That we're almost home?", "question_tokens": ["That", "we", "'re", "almost", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "LOVE: When we could see land.", "answer_tokens": ["LOVE", ":", "When", "we", "could", "see", "land", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And not to say you're the trouble maker, but this did not go in any way that this family thought, did it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "not", "to", "say", "you", "'re", "the", "trouble", "maker", ",", "but", "this", "did", "not", "go", "in", "any", "way", "that", "this", "family", "thought", ",", "did", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "No, but it was 2 1/2 days of great fun, and then the rest of the time, it was family coming together, bonding.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "it", "was", "2", "1/2", "days", "of", "great", "fun", ",", "and", "then", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "time", ",", "it", "was", "family", "coming", "together", ",", "bonding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Did you really feel the rough seas?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "feel", "the", "rough", "seas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "At times, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "times", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "And how do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Grounded.", "answer_tokens": ["Grounded", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Has it finally sunk in?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "finally", "sunk", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "No, when we were standing at the doors, I said, it still doesn't seem like it's happening.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "when", "we", "were", "standing", "at", "the", "doors", ",", "I", "said", ",", "it", "still", "does", "n't", "seem", "like", "it", "'s", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "What do you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Pray.", "answer_tokens": ["Pray", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Did you meet new people through that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "meet", "new", "people", "through", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Yes, yes, we did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "What happens after the sun goes down?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "after", "the", "sun", "goes", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "It was creepy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "creepy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "So will you ever go again?", "question_tokens": ["So", "will", "you", "ever", "go", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "Probably not.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "How do you get that out of your mind?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "that", "out", "of", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "I probably won't, but I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "probably", "wo", "n't", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Are you friends or dating?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "friends", "or", "dating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "We're friends.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "How did you spend the time?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "spend", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "A lot of cards were played.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "cards", "were", "played", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Was it there?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "The first day, we slept at 6:00.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "day", ",", "we", "slept", "at", "6:00", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "You think everyone got along well?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "everyone", "got", "along", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "Not everybody.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "everybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Was there an organization to the day?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "an", "organization", "to", "the", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "We tried to sleep a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "tried", "to", "sleep", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "Are you going to save the robe?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "save", "the", "robe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]